<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="106">
    <author>Willi Willswissen</author>
	<contributors>AutoDrive Team</contributors>
    <version>3.0.1.0</version>
    <title> 
        <en>AD-Intersections AiO</en>
        <de>AD-Kreuzungen AiO</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en> <![CDATA[

Placeable Crossings
With this mod you can build a finished AD intersection on the map.
In the construction menu under Decorations - Other you will find four X and T intersections with track widths of 3m, 4m, 5m and 6m.
These intersections have a positioning aid (yellow cross) to align them.
If you leave the construction menu after placing them, the waypoints of an AD intersection are created with a destination point in the middle.
You can then connect these to your route network. The yellow cross can be sold again via the construction menu.
You should delete the destination points of the intersections again after completing the routes, otherwise they will influence the route calculation
by AutoDrive. They are very useful for creating routes, as they allow you to drive directly to every intersection with AutoDrive.
You need a mod that allows placement on land that does not belong to you.

Changelog:
V1.0.0.1
- changed collision mask
V1.1.0.0
- revised design for the right-of-way rule
V3.0.1.0
- revised design for the right-of-way rules with green lines introduced in AutoDrive 3.0.1.0

]]>
        </en>
        <de> <![CDATA[

Platzierbare Kreuzungen
Mit diesem Mod könnt ihr euch eine fertige AD Kreuzung auf der Map bauen.
Ihr findet im Baumenü unter Dekorationen - Sonstiges vier X und T Kreuzungen mit den Spurweiten 3m, 4m, 5m und 6m.
Diese Kreuzungen haben eine Positionierhilfe (gelbes Kreuz) um sie auszurichten.
Verlasst ihr nach der Platzierung das Baumenü, werden die Wegpunkte einer AD Kreuzung mit einem Zielpunkt in der Mitte angelegt.
Ihr könnt diese dann mit eurem Streckennetz verbinden. Das gelbe Kreuz kann über des Baumenü wieder verkauft werden.
Die Zielpunkte der Kreuzungen solltet ihr nach Fertigstellung der Routen wieder löschen, da sie sonst Einfluss auf die Wegberechnung
von AutoDrive haben. Zur Erstellung der Routen sind sie ganz nützlich, da sich so mit AutoDrive jede Kreuzung direkt anfahren läßt.
Ihr braucht einen Mod, der das Platzieren auf Land erlaubt, das euch nicht gehört.

Changelog:
V1.0.0.1
- geänderte Kollisions-Maske
V1.1.0.0
- überarbeitetes Design für die Vorfahrtsregelung
V3.0.1.0
- überarbeitetes Design für die Vorfahrtsregelung mit grünen Linien eingeführt in Autodrive 3.0.1.0

]]>
        </de>
    </description>
    
    <l10n>
        <text name="storeItem_xcrossing-3m-line"> <en>AD-X-AiO 3m with lines</en> <de>AD-X-AiO 3m mit Hilfslinien</de> </text>
        <text name="storeItem_xcrossing-4m-line"> <en>AD-X-AiO 4m with lines</en> <de>AD-X-AiO 4m mit Hilfslinien</de> </text>
        <text name="storeItem_xcrossing-5m-line"> <en>AD-X-AiO 5m with lines</en> <de>AD-X-AiO 5m mit Hilfslinien</de> </text>
        <text name="storeItem_xcrossing-6m-line"> <en>AD-X-AiO 6m with lines</en> <de>AD-X-AiO 6m mit Hilfslinien</de> </text>
        <text name="storeItem_tcrossing-3m-line"> <en>AD-T-AiO 3m with lines</en> <de>AD-T-AiO 3m mit Hilfslinien</de> </text>
        <text name="storeItem_tcrossing-4m-line"> <en>AD-T-AiO 4m with lines</en> <de>AD-T-AiO 4m mit Hilfslinien</de> </text>
        <text name="storeItem_tcrossing-5m-line"> <en>AD-T-AiO 5m with lines</en> <de>AD-T-AiO 5m mit Hilfslinien</de> </text>
        <text name="storeItem_tcrossing-6m-line"> <en>AD-T-AiO 6m with lines</en> <de>AD-T-AiO 6m mit Hilfslinien</de> </text>
    </l10n>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <iconFilename>icon_AutoDrive_xCrossing.png</iconFilename>

    <storeItems>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xcrossing-3m-line.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xcrossing-4m-line.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xcrossing-5m-line.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xcrossing-6m-line.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="tcrossing-3m-line.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="tcrossing-4m-line.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="tcrossing-5m-line.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="tcrossing-6m-line.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
</modDesc>